Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series IA: General Files, A-H
  - Commonwealth Edison Company, Dresden Nuclear Power Station, 1961-1962 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Communication, Committee on, recomposed, 1956-1962 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Communism, 1961-1968 (Box 111, Folder 5-6)
  - Communist Party, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Community and Family Study Center, 1963-1965 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Community and Family Study Center, space needs and accommodations, 1962-1966 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Community Fund of Chicago, annual campaign drive, 1961-1964 (Box 111, Folder 10-12)
  - Community Health Affairs and Hospitals, Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Community and Real Estate Office, Neighborhood Committee, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Community Renewal Society, 1964-1968 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Compact for Education and Education Commission of the States, 1965-1967 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Comparative Education Center, 1964-1967 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Comparative Education Center, reports of, activities, 1961-1964 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Comparative Studies in Literature, Committee on, 1966-1968 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Comparative Study of New Nations, Committee for, 1963-1968 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller, 1961-1962 (Box 112, Folder 8-9)
  - Comptroller, 1963-1966 (Box 113, Folder 1-2)
  - Comptroller, Harvey C. Daines, 1950-1966 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 1967-1968 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller, Office of, (J. I. Kirkpatrick, D. L. Cartland, and A. Lincicome), 1951-1967 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller, possible candidates for position, 1964-1965 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Computation Center, 1961-1968 (Box 113, Folder 7-9)
  - Computation Center, 7044-7094, 1963-1968 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
  - Computation Center, Biological Sciences, 1962-1966 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Computation Center, dedication of new IBM computer 7090, 1961-1962 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Computation Center, directorship, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Computation Center, IBM 360 Model 65 and IBM 360 Model 67, 1962-1966 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Computation Center, IBM 7040 computer, 1964-1967 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Computer activities, 1961-1962 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Computer Center, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Computer Facility, Inter-University Committee to Study Feasibility of, 1967-1968 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Computer Policy Committee, 1962-1065 (Box 115, Folder 3-6)
  - Computer Policy Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 116, Folder 1-5)
  - Computer Policy Committee, membership, 1962-1968 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Computer Policy Committee, minutes of meetings, 1962-1968 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Computer Policy Committee, operations and costs, 1960-1963 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Computer Research Building, basement extension, construction and financing, 1962-1967 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Computer Research Building, construction and financing, 1954-1963 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Computers, 1960-1965 (Box 117, Folder 5-7)
  - Con-, general, 1964-1965 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Cone, Fairfax M., blue streak memos, essays, 1963-1967 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Abortion (national), 1968 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Mainland China, 1965-1966 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion, 1963-1966 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Congregation Rodfei Zedek, 1963-1964 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Congregational Church of Western Springs, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Congress of Scientists on Survival, 1961-1964 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Context, new University of Chicago magazine for non-alumni, 1961-1964 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Continuing Education report, 1965-1967 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Contractual and financial management and operation of large residential centers by educational institutions, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Convocation, 1961-1963 (Box 118, Folder 4-9)
  - Convocation, 1964-1968 (Box 119, Folder 1-5)
  - Convocation luncheons, 1961-1965 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Convocation programs, June 7 and 8, 1968 and August 30, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Convocation receptions, 1962-1965 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Convocation speakers, 1961-1968 (Box 120, Folder 1-5)
  - Convocation speakers, selection, 1961-1967 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Convocation speech, Lawrence Kimpton, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Cook County, Coroner's Citizen's Advisory Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Cook County, general, 1961-1967 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Cook County Hospital, 1962-1967 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Cooperation Program for Educational Opportunity, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Copacetic, origin of word, 1962 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Cor-, general, 1963-1966 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University, 1961-1968 (Box 121, Folder 3-6)
  - Cosmos Club, 1964-1968 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Cosmos Club Awards, 1963-1968 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Council for the Advancement of Science Writing, 1962-1965 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Council for Community Services in Metropolitan Chicago, 1965-1968 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Council of Graduate Schools in the United States, 1961-1967 (Box 121, Folder 11-12)
  - Council of State Governments, 1962-1967 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Council for the Study of Mankind, 1963-1964 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Council on Teacher Education, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Council of Ten and the University of Chicago, Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1960-1967 (Box 122, Folder 4-5)
  - Council of Ten and the University of Chicago, Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Anthropology, Human Ecology, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Council of the University Senate, 1962-1967 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Council of the University Senate, elections and membership, 1961-1968 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Counseling Center, general, 1961-1967 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Country Home for Convalescent Children, Boards of Trustees, managers, members, 1961-1965 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Country Home for Convalescent Children, budget and finance, 1961-1965 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Court Theater, 1967-1968 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Court Theater, Committee on the, (faculty advisory), 1966-1968 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Court Theater, the Misanthrope, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Credit Unions, university staff, 1961-1967 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Crime in the university area, Gutmann, Roy Dennis, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Crusade of Mercy campaign, 1960-1963 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Cu-, general, 1964-1965 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Cuba, 1961-1966 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Cyclotron, 1962-1965 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1963-1966 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - D-, general, 1963-1965 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Daly, Charles U., personal, A-z, 1965-1968 (Box 123, Folder 10-12)
  - Dames Club of the University of Chicago, 1957-1965 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Dartmouth College, 1961-1963 (Box 124, Folder 2-3)
  - Dav-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Day Care Center, proposed non-profit corporation, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - De-, general, 1963-1965 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Dean of Students, 1961-1968 (Box 124, Folder 7-10)
  - Dean of Students, Committee to Evaluate the Current Policies and Practices of the Office of, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Dean of Students, letters to parents, 1964-1967 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Dean of Students Office, space, 1966 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Dean of students, study of information processing and record keeping activities in office of, 1963 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Deans, 1961-1965 (Box 124, Folder 15-17)
  - Deans, 1966-1967 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Deans, annual reports (proposed), 1963-1968 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Deans, directors, chairman, (Masters), lists of, 1936-1965 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Deans of Graduate Schools, list of, 1965 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Deans' meetings, 1961-1968 (Box 125, Folder 5-8)
  - Deans, memo masters, 1963-1966 (Box 126, Folder 1-4)
  - Deans' select group (Harvard, Yale, Princeton, Columbia, and small group of others outside the east), 1965-1967 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Decentralization, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Degree approval slips, 1965-1968 (Box 126, Folder 7-17)
  - Degree approval slips, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
  - Degrees, Committee on, requirements for the PhD, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Degrees, Committee on a three year masters program, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Degrees, diploma mills, 1961-1964 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Degrees, general, 1962-1968 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Degrees, joint programs, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Degrees, lists of candidates for, 1961-1967 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Degrees, masters of theology and doctor of ministry, Divinity School, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Degrees, PhD, proposal to reduce time required for, 1966-1968 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Degrees, PhD statistics, 1961-1967 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Degrees, registration with the State of Illinois legislation, 1961-1962 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - De Kiewiet, Cornelis W., 1961 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Demonstrations, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Demonstrations, campus unrest, 1965-1968 (Box 128, Folder 1-2)
  - Demonstrations, class rank and Selective, Service, 1966-1967 (Box 128, Folder 3-4)
  - Demonstrations, Diary of the Sit-Ins, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Demonstrations, Diary of the Sit-Ins, 1962 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Demonstrations, Dow recruitment visit on campus, 1967-1968 (Box 129, Folder 2-3)
  - Demonstrations, Fair Housing Alliance, tent in, housing for students and community people, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Demonstrations, housing, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Demonstrations, Michigan State and University of Michigan, 1963-1967 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Demonstrations, outside comments on, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Demonstrations, statements, demands, May 15, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Demonstrator's Association of Illinois, 1961-1967 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Denver, University of, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - De Paul University, 1963-1965 (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
  - Development, 1961-1968 (Box 130, Folder 3-8)
  - Di-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Dickerson, James Spencer, 1932-1966 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Disciples Divinity House, 1961-1967 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Disruptive demonstrations, disciplinary committee, 1963-1967 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Divinity School, 1961-1964 (Box 130, Folder 13-14)
  - Divinity School, 1965-1968 (Box 131, Folder 1-3)
  - Divinity School, 100th anniversary celebration year, 1965-1966 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Divinity School, Criterion, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Divinity School, Interdenominational Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Divinity School, "Perspectives on the Good Society" A Jewish Protestant Colloquium, April 23, 1963 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Divinity School, Special Theological Conference, Dr. Karl Barth lectures, 1961-1962 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Divinity School, statistics, 1963-1965 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Divinity School, visiting committee, 1964-1968 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Dormitories, general, 1964-1965 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Dormitories, invitations to officers of the President's Office to visit, 1961-1968 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Dormitories, Pierce Hall, 1961-1966 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Dormitories, Pierce Hall, budget and finance, 1961-1968 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, 1961-1967 (Box 132, Folder 4-5)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, budget and finance, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, Nurses' residences, 6022 Drexel Avenue, 1961-1968 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, Nurses' residences, 6104 Woodlawn Avenue, 1961-1963 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, Nurses' residences, proposed, 1962-1968 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, Pierce Hall, 1961-1966 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, The Village, proposed, 1965-1967 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, Woodward Court, 1961-1965 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, buildings, Woodward Court, budget and finance, 1961-1965 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, food service, contracts and surveys, 1961-1968 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, house system and student life, Newman report, 1963 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, Inter-House council, 1965-1967 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Dormitories and residence halls, Snell-Hitchcock Hall, 1961-1966 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Dr-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Dream research, 1961-1962 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Drug use and abuse at the University, media mention and publications, 1965-1967 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Duke University, 1963-1965 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - E-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1961-1966 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 133, Folder 11-12)
  - Economics, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 133, Folder 13-16)
  - Economics of the major private university, 1967-1968 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Economics of the major private university, 1967-1968 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Economics of the University, Advisory Committee on, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Economics of a university, general, 1963-1968 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Christian Council at the University of Chicago, 1968 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Editorial Projects for Education, Fifteen minute report (for College and University Trustees), 1964-1967 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Editorial Projects for Education, the "Moonshooter" report, 1958-1966 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Education, Department of, 1960-1968 (Box 134, Folder 7-12)
  - Education, Department of, annual reading conferences, 1961-1966 (Box 134, Folder 13-14)
  - Education, Department of, conferences, seminars and workshops, 1964-1968 (Box 135, Folder 1-2)
  - Education, Department and Graduate School of, 1961-1964 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Education, Department and Graduate School of, accreditation, 1964 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Education, Department and Graduate School of, Pakistan Education Project, 1962-1968 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Education Department, guidance conference, 1961 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Education, Department of, space, 1965-1967 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Education, Department of, Student-Faculty Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Education, Graduate School of, 1961-1966 (Box 135, Folder 9-12)
  - Education, Graduate School of, accreditation, 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 1-2)
  - Education, Graduate School of, deanship, 1963-1966 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Education, Graduate School of, Faculty Board, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Education, Graduate School of, lecture series, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Education for Mankind Conference, April 5-11, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Educational Committee to Halt Atomic Weapons Spread, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Educational Policies Commission, 1940-1965 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Educational Services Incorporated, 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1960-1963 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - El-, general, 1964-1968 (Box 136, Folder 11-12)
  - Electronic Representative Association, 1963 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965, 1965-1968 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Elmhurst College, 1963-1967 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Emancipation Centennial Authority, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Emeritus, appointments, 1960-1962 (Box 137, Folder 4-5)
  - Emeritus, appointments, post-retirement, 1963-1965 (Box 137, Folder 6-7)
  - Emery Drexel Livery, 1961-1965 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Emory University, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, Advisory Committee, membership, 1961-1967 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Endowment funds, comparative studies and articles, 1960-1968 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Engineering College Research Council, 1960-1962 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - English, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 138, Folder 3-7)
  - English, Department of, constitution, revised, 1963 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - English Language and Literature, Department of, chairmanship, 1961-1966 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1962-1964 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Ep-, general, 1964-1968 (Box 138, Folder 11-12)
  - Episcopal Church, Episcopal Student Center (Brent House), 1964-1967 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Equipment, policies and procedures, 1961-1968 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - European Atomic Energy Commission (Euratom), The Commission (publication), 1962-1965 (Box 138, Folder 15-16)
  - Evolutionary Biology, Committee on, 1963-1968 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Exam schedule, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Examiner, Office of, 1961-1963 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Executive Club of Chicago, 1961-1962 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Faculties, Secretary of, 1961 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Faculty, 1961-1962 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Faculty assistance loan program, 1962-1967 (Box 139, Folder 7-11)
  - Faculty handbook, 1965 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Faculty honors and memberships in national societies, 1963-1967 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Faculty losses, resignations, retirements and terminations, 1960-1967 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Faculty losses, resignations, retirements, terminations, gains and losses, survey, 1962 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Faculty newcomers program, 1960-1966 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Faculty News Bulletin, 1962 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Faculty News Bulletin, general, 1962 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Faculty recruitment, 1962-1967 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Student Advisory Committee on Campus Student Life, 1966-1967 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Student Committees of the University, membership, 1966-1967 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Student Informal Social Rules, Committee on, (Dean's), 1966-1968 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Faculty of the University, evaluations, 1962-1964 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Faculty of the University, teaching loads, 1965-1967 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Voice, a newsletter, 1966-1968 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Wives' Dinner, 1960-1968 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Wives of the University Information Committee, 1963 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Wives of the University tea series, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Far Eastern Languages and Civilizations, Department of, 1936-1964 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Far Eastern Studies, Committee on, 1963 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Faulkner School, the, 1958-1968 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1961-1965 (Box 141, Folder 1-3)
  - Federal Aid to Education, general, 1960-1968 (Box 141, Folder 4-5)
  - Federal Bar Association, 1958-1962 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Federal City Council, 1961-1964 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Federal Tax Conference, 1961-1968 (Box 141, Folder 8-10)
  - Federation of Illinois Colleges, 1961 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Illinois Colleges, annual meetings materials, 1961-1964 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Independent Illinois Colleges and Universities, 1965-1967 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Independent Illinois Colleges and Universities, annual meeting materials, 1964-1967 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Independent Illinois Colleges and Universities, master plan, phase two controversy, 1964-1967 (Box 142, Folder 3-5)
  - Federation of Independent Illinois Colleges and Universities, meetings, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, 1962-1969 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Fees, 1961-1967 (Box 142, Folder 7-8)
  - Fees, 1962-1968 (Box 143, Folder 1-5)
  - Fees, actual income, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Fees, history of regulations, 1927-1965 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Fees, plan for eliminating tuition, 1967 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Feldstein, Charles R. and Company, agreements and contracts, 1961-1967 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Fermi, Enrico, Institute, directorship, 1963-1968 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Fermi Institute dinner, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Festival of the Arts (FOTA), 1961-1968 (Box 143, Folder 12-15)
  - Field Museum of Natural History, Center for Graduate Studies, Advisory Board, 1965-1967 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Fifth Ward Citizens' Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Financial Management Information System, proposed study of the University of Chicago by Touche, Ross, Baily, and Smart, 1966-1967 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Financial policy and program, 1961-1965 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Financial report, 1965-1968 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Financing higher education, a proposal to provide basic needs, 1967 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Fine Arts Center, building, proposed, 1961-1964 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Fiscal year, possible change, 1961-1963 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Florence Agreement, National Committee for, 1965-1967 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Florida State University, 1959-1963 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Food Research Institute, 1961-1966 (Box 144, Folder 10-11)
  - Food Research Institute, building and space, 1940-1964 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Food Research Institute, directorship, 1961-1966 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Food Research Institute, food industry proposal for support, 1961-1962 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Food Research Institute, Quartermaster Food and Container Institute, 1961 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Food Research Institute, transfer to University of Wisconsin, 1964-1966 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Food service, 1960-1968 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Food service, Hutchinson Commons, 1962-1968 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Food service, Hutchinson Commons and C shop, Stouffer's food service management agreement, 1966-1968 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Food service at the University, dormitories and residence halls, DeLue, Mary Elizabeth, vs. the University of Chicago, 1962-1968 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Food service at the University, Hutchinson Commons, C shop closing, 1963-1967 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Food service at the University, Ida Noyes Hall, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Food service at the University, Ida Noyes Hall, "Bandersnatch," 1966-1968 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Football, general, 1961-1968 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Ford Foundation, 1965 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Medical Scholars, Conference for, June 24-27, 1962 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Fortune Magazine, 1961-1967 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Foundation for Human Ecology, Park Ridge Illinois, 1961 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Four E contracts, salaries and related statistics, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Four quarter system, 1961-1964 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - France, visitors to the University from, 1963-1966 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Franck, James, Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Franck, James, Institute for the Study of Metals, 1961-1967 (Box 146, Folder 3-4)
  - Franck Memorial Symposium, Committee to Organize a, 1965-1966 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Frankfurt-Chicago Inter-University Project, 1961-1965 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Frankfurt, University of, Chicago-Frankfurt Interuniversity Project, 1961-1964 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Fraternities, 1960-1967 (Box 146, Folder 8-9)
  - Fraternities, Committee on, 1958-1964 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Fraternities, Gamma Alpha and Phi Delta Theta, 1961-1965 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Fraternities and sororities, Beta Theta Pi, 1965 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Fraternities and sororities, Interfraternity Council, 1961-1965 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Fraternities, university policy, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Freedom House, 1961-1968 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Funding proposals, application for Title IV NDEA fellowships, 1965-1967 (Box 147, Folder 2-3)
  - Funding proposals, application for Title IV NDEA fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Funding proposals, Social Services Center, 1966-1967 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Funds, reserve and suspense, statements, 1961-1968 (Box 148, Folder 3)